[Music]
road is wide sky is
black rattlesnake run down your
back there's a house like
Mo bang bang bang bo bo
bo why you love oh I want your
love I want your boys in my
C
morning
ring bang bang
bang bang bang in a ring of
fire bang bang my sweet
the bang bang my love is true
bang bang I D for
you bang bang bang bo
[Music]
b so count it down from 10 to
one crazy high lucky
gun we were born that Blood and Bone
you're the six and I am the
stone bang
bang ring
of bang bang my sweet
Des bang bang my love is
true bang bang I die for
you bang bang bang
[Music]
Happ be B you be C Rock and Roll Suicide
meet you on the other
side bu me from Silver Spoons I got them
baby just for you oh right yeah and may
your
move do a s
[Music]
[Applause]
bang bang in a ring of the
fire bang bang my sweet
design bang bang I love this
true bang bang I di for you
bang
bang bang
bangang oh bang
[Music]
bang and an X bang bang might be for you